http://www.lulop.com/en_EN/privacy-policy

Lulop.com Privacy Policy
Lulop.com is pleased to have you visit our Internet sites and welcomes your interest in our company and our products.
Intellectual property
All materials on this website are the sole property of their respective brand or of a third party having granted Lulop.com limited permission to use them.
All materials posted on this site may only be: reprinted, broadcasted or published online by legitimate, professional news organizations for editorial use only.
Any other use is strictly forbidden without respective brand's prior written agreement.
All trademarks are the ownership of their respective owners.
Lulop.com respects your privacy
The protection of your privacy in the processing of your personal data is an important concern to which we pay special attention during our business processes. We process personal data collected during your visit to our websites confidentially and solely in compliance with legal provisions.
Data protection and information security are part of our corporate policy.
Collection and processing of personal data
Personal data is only stored when voluntarily given by you for a determined purpose e.g. in context of a registration, a survey, a contest or in performance of a contract.
In addition the following information is collected when visiting our website: IP addresses, the website from which you visit us (referrer), pages viewed, files downloaded (downloads), videos viewed/audio tracks listened to, individual links clicked, search words or search phrases (site search), duration of visit, browser used, etc.
The insights gained enable us to further optimize our websites and tailor them even better to our visitors' needs.
Type of data collected
Among the Personal data collected by lulop.com, there are: email, name, surname, telephone number, company, role, reason for registration to the Lulop platform, publication, media type, platform data usage, website and cookies.
All data requested by Lulop.com are mandatory and, failing this, it may be impossible to provide the service. In the event that Lulop.com indicates some data as optional, users are free to refrain from communicating such data, this will have no consequences on the availability of the service or on its operation.
Users who have doubts about which data are required can contact the data owner.
Any use of cookies - or other tracking tools - by this Application or third party service providers used by lulop.com, is intended to provide the service requested by the user, in addition to the other purposes described in this document and in the cookie policy.
Lulop.com does not collect any datas when files attached have been downloaded from the platform.
The user is reliable for personal data of third parties that he has published or shared through lulop.com and guarantees to have the right to communicate or disseminate them, freeing the owner from any liability to third parties.
Purposes of treatment
The user's data are collected for the owner to provide his services, as well as for the following purposes: contacting the user, sending notifications concerning the activity of the Lulop platform performed on its own or by its customers, reports both for internal use and for the use of Lulop.com customers, Lulop.com platform administration.
Method of treatment
The owner processes users personal by adopting appropriate security measures to prevent access, disclosure, modification or unauthorized distribution of personal data.
Processing is carried out using IT and / or telematic tools, with organizational methods
strictly related to the purposes above mentioned. In addition to the owner, in some cases, categories of assignments (administrative staff, marketing, legal, system administrators, drafting staff) or external subjects (as suppliers of third party technical services, agencies communication and press offices of the Lulop platform), may have access to data involved in the organization of the site.
Personal Data collected by lulop.com, are registered in Lulop.com proprietary DB hosted by Google Cloud Storage (hosting service provided by Google Inc.).
User data access is granted to authorized persons only, in accordance to their level of platform operation.
Use of cookies
1) Lulop.com cookies
Lulop.com uses cookies and active components (e.g. JavaScript) to track visitors‘ preferences and customise the design of the websites.
Cookies are small text files stored on your computer when you visit our website. If you like, you can delete the cookies at any time. However, this can result in some functions no longer being available. For information on deleting the cookies, please consult your browser‘s help function.
2) Third-party cookies
Lulop.com incorporate content and services from other providers (Facebook, AddThis) who, in turn, may use cookies and active components. Lulop.com has no influence on the processing of personal data by these providers.
Please refer to the respective provider‘s websites for information about how your data is handled.
See our cookie policy
Use of the Google analytics tool
Lulop.com uses the Google analytics tool to carry out access measurements.
The access data is collected in anonymized form so that it can no longer be traced back to a user. In particular, this is done by anonymizing the IP address.
Cookies are used for metrics to enable website usage to be analyzed. In particular, Lulop.com uses them to improve data quality. The information generated by the use of Lulop.com is transmitted anonymized to the google Analytics server. google analytics it’s a Google Inc. services, 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, USA ("Google").
Use of social plugins as part of social media
Addthis is a service provided by Clearspring Technologies Inc. that, allows lulop.com content sharing to interact with social networks and external platform through a widget.
Depending on the settings, this service can show third parties action and performances that have taken paces through the widgets (e.g. content sharing on social networks)
Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data. Place of processing: USA
Lulop.com uses social plugins ("plugins") from the social network Facebook.com, which is operated by Facebook Inc., Palo Alto, CA, USA ("Facebook"). The plugins are identified with the button “publish on facebook”.
If you visit a page on our website that contains such plugins, they are initially disabled. The plugins are not enabled unless you click the button that is provided. By enabling the plugins, you establish the connection to Facebook and declare your consent to the transmission of data to Facebook. If you are logged into Facebook, Facebook can associate the visit with your Facebook account. If you press the previoustly described button, the corresponding information is transmitted directly to Facebook by your browser and stored there.
For information about the scope and purpose of data collection, the further processing and use of the data by Facebook, and your rights and settings to protect your privacy, please refer to Facebook Data Protection Notice.
If you do not want Facebook to collect data about you via our website, you have to log out from Facebook before visiting our site.
Use of external links
Lulop.com may contain links to third-party websites operated by providers that are not associated with us. Lulop does not respond for any collection of datas, storage, or processing of any personal data (such as the IP address or URL of the page that contains the link) when action occurs by clicking external links , as the behaviour of third parties is, by nature, beyond our control. Therefore, Lulop.com is not responsible for the processing of personal data by third parties after you click the link described above.
Security
Lulop.com takes security precautions to ensure that your data with us is protected against tampering, loss, destruction, access by unauthorised persons, or unauthorised disclosure. Our security measures are being continuously improved in accordance with the state of technological developments.
Consent revocation
You can also revoke your consent to the collection, processing, and use of your personal data for the future.
In case the consent is revoked, if storage of personal data for the performance of the purpose is no longer necessary or if the storage of the personal data is inadmissible due to other legal reasons, the personal data will be deleted.
In case of consent revoking it is no longer possible to use Lulop.com services.
Due to the professional nature of the service, actions such as media download, notification and other services, can’t be anonymous.
Following the withdrawal of consent, the account will deleted, with exception for
the numerical ID that will remain stored in the activity logs, in order to allow an accurate activity analysis. After the revocation, the numeric ID will no longer be locked to personal information and data logs kept anonymous.
Data necessary for billing and accounting purposes or bye legal obligation is not affected by the above described.
Contact
To obtain more informations or to submit suggestions or complaints regarding the processing of your personal data, you can contact our chief officer corporate data security.
If incorrect information has been stored despite our efforts to store correct and current data, we will correct this upon your request.
VIDEOPR S.R.L.
I declare that I have read, understood and accepted the terms set out in the privacy policy
